(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
んらぁぁぁ
Nraaaa
みんな
Everyone
おりゅ〜？
Are you here?
ななのら〜！
Na-nanora~!
絶対忠誠♡ななのら！
Absolute Loyalty ♡ Nanonora!
お菓子の国の お姫様
I'm a princess from the Candy Kingdom
とびきりプリティな 0歳児
A super pretty 0-year-old
ピアノだって 弾けるんだし
I can even play the piano
赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
I'm not a baby, nora!
ワガママだって 言うけれど
You say I'm selfish, but
ルーナはお姫様なのだから
Luna is a princess after all
ルーナイト達も 執事も
Both my LuKnights and my butler
いちいちうるさいのら！
Are so noisy about everything, nora!
さぁ ルーナイト達！
Now, LuKnights!
準備はできたのら？
Are you ready, nora?
出陣なのら〜！
Time to head out, nora!
パフェも しゅわしゅわも
Parfaits and fizzy drinks...
早く用意するのら！
Hurry up and get them ready, nora!
あれもこれもお 食べたいのら！
I want to eat this and that, nora!
おいしいのは 独り占め
I'll keep the tasty stuff all for myself
まずいのや
The bad ones
苦いのは ルーナイト達に
And the bitter ones...
差し入れ★
I'll give to you LuKnights! ★
チョコレートの噴水も
Chocolate fountains
キャンディの首飾りも
And candy necklaces too
素敵なの たくさんあるのら
There are so many wonderful things, nora
だからルーナのために 集めて来てね
So please go and gather them for Luna
絶対 絶対 絶対 約束
It's a promise, definitely, definitely, definitely
ななのら〜！
Nanonora~!
ぐるぐる＠まわる＠まわルナ
Gurguru @ Mawaru @ Mawaruna
まわる まわる まわる まわルナ
Spin, spin, spin, Mawaruna
まわる まわる まわる まわルナ なのら！
Spin, spin, spin, Mawaruna nanora!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回って
Round and round and round and round, spin
もっとぐるぐる回って
Spin even more, round and round
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回って
Round and round and round and round, spin
みんなぐるぐる回って
Everyone, spin round and round
ぐるぐるぐるぐるそら回って
Round and round and round and round, there you go
もっとぐるぐる回って
Spin even more, round and round
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回って
Round and round and round and round, spin
ずっとぐるぐる回ルナ！
Forever spinning, Mawaruna!
ぐるぐる地球は 回り始め幾億年
Round and round, the Earth has been spinning for billions of years
いつまでもこのまま
Just like this, forever
回るみんなに幸せを...
Happiness to everyone who spins...
まわり続ける まわルナ
Spinning on and on, Mawaruna
ますますますます世界が
More and more and more and more, the world...
ぐるぐるま〜
Round and round we go~
あれ？
Oh?
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回って
Round and round and round and round, spin
もっとぐるぐる回って
Spin even more, round and round
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回って
Round and round and round and round, spin
みんなぐるぐる回って
Everyone, spin round and round
ぐるぐるぐるぐる笑って
Round and round and round and round, laugh
もっとぐるぐる笑って
Laugh even more, round and round
ぐるぐるぐるぐる踊って
Round and round and round and round, dance
みんなぐるぐる踊って
Everyone, dance round and round
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回って
Round and round and round and round, spin...
もっと
More
ぐーるぐーるぐーるぐーる まわってんの～
Spinning round and round and round and round~
ぐるぐるまわる まわる まわる の～ら やぁ
Spinning round and round, round and round, nanora, yaa
いつもおとぎ話のお姫様 みんなの輝くお月様
Always a fairy tale princess, everyone's shining moon
今日はお休みして 重い王冠 今は置いて
Take a break today, put down that heavy crown for now
どっちの私も 好きになってくれますか？
Will you come to love both versions of me?
どっちも欲しいから まんなかにいたくなるの
Because I want both, I want to be in the middle
スニーカーと シャツに着替えて
Changing into sneakers and a shirt
歩き出したんだ
I've started walking
出発のアラームを
I'll ring the departure alarm
新しい私が鳴らしてあげる
The new me will ring it for you
両腕を いっぱいにしても ぎゅっとしたい
Even with my arms full, I want to hold you tight
この気持ち 入らない
This feeling won't fit inside
片っぽ なんて選べない
I can't choose just one side
迷ってるなら まんなかなんだよ
If you're lost, just stay in the middle
満開の青春
Youth in full bloom
満腹に摂取
Taking it all in until full
満天流星群
A perfect meteor shower
満遍にheaven
Heaven all around
満面に笑顔にして
Put a smile on your face
満点すぎる思い出
Memories that are more than perfect
まーる まるっと Happy day!
A round and round Happy day!
君のまんなかで
Right in your center!
プリンセスを 忘れるくらい
So much that you almost forget I'm a princess
胸まんたんに きゅんっとしてみたい
I want my heart to feel full and fluttery
どっちだって ホントの私
Both versions are the real me
瞬きしたら 君のどまんなか
If you blink, I'll be right in your center
まんなかにかさなっちてん
Overlapping in the middle
まんなかでよくばっちてん
Being greedy in the middle
まんなかのまんなかちてん
The center of the center
恋する女の子の いいとこ取りで
Taking only the best parts of a girl in love
照れ隠しと 素直の今
Hiding my blush and being honest, right now
まんなかちてん
In the middle
跪きなさい。
Kneel before me.
汝、この城の扉を叩いたものよ。
Thou who hast knocked upon the gates of this castle.
誓いなさい。
Swear thy path.
このルーナの盾となり矛となり。
To be the shield and the spear for Luna.
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで。
Until you fall fast asleep at night.
共にあることをー！
We shall be together!
捧げなさい！
Devote yourselves!
姫であるぞ！
For I am the Princess!
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Luna-knight
止まるな
Don't stop
紅茶のカップ かちゃかちゃ鳴らさないって
Good job not clinking your teacup!
えらい！
Good job!
スコーンだって こぼさず 綺麗に食べて
Amazing job eating your scones without spilling a crumb!
すごい！
Amazing!
たまーに王冠 どっちが前か 間違っちゃうの
Sometimes you get your crown on backwards
かわいい！
How cute!
通ってよし なのら
You may pass, nanora
開城ー！
Open the gates!
ルーナイト 第一条
Luna-knight Clause 1
誰よりルーナが 好きな人
One who loves Luna more than anyone else
ルーナイト 第二条
Luna-knight Clause 2
シルクのお布団 持ってきて
Bring me my silk bedding
ルーナイト 第三条
Luna-knight Clause 3
三時のお茶会 来れる人
One who can attend the 3 PM tea party
守れなかったら 即制裁！
If you fail to comply, immediate punishment!
分かってほしいのら
I want you to understand, nanora
これも 帝王学を学ぶため
This is all part of my imperial studies
愛という名の
In the name of love
教育なのらー！
It's education, nanora!
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Luna-knight
想ってくんないと
If you don't keep me in your thoughts
プロムナード ボイコット なのなののら
I'll boycott the promenade, nano-nano-nora!
手の甲に忠誠 誓えるの？
Can you swear loyalty on the back of my hand?
チュッ
(Chu!)
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Put on my glass slippers and let's waltz!
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Luna-knight
かまってくんないと
If you don't pay attention to me
ブラウニーにキャンディー
Brownies and candies
どれだけあってもね
No matter how many I have
君がいなきゃ だって
...it's no good without you!
みんな 心して
Everyone, brace yourselves
捧げなさい！
Devote yourselves!
姫であるぞ！
For I am the Princess!
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Luna-knight
想ってくんないと
If you don't keep me in your thoughts
プロムナード ボイコット なのなののら
I'll boycott the promenade, nano-nano-nora!
永遠の忠誠 この指に
Swear eternal loyalty on this finger
チュッ
(Chu!)
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Put on my glass slippers and let's waltz!
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Luna-knight
かまってくんないと
If you don't pay attention to me
ブラウニーにキャンディー
Brownies and candies
どれだけあってもね
No matter how many I have
君がいなきゃ だって
...it's no good without you!
みんな 心して
Everyone, brace yourselves
捧げなさい！
Devote yourselves!
姫であるぞ！
For I am the Princess!
のらー！
Nora!
みんな、およー！
Hello everyone!
ほらライブ4期生、姫森ルーナなのののな。
I'm Himemori Luna from Hololive Gen 4, nano-nano-na.
今日は、ルーナの生誕祭ライブ！
Today is Luna's Birthday Live!
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんな来てくれてありがとのら。
Thank you all for coming.
今日のハッシュタグはこちら。
Today's hashtag is this one.
デデン！
Ta-da!
#姫森ルーナ生誕ライブ2025
#LunaRebirthDay2025
これでいっぱいツイートしてください。
Please tweet a lot with this.
ほい！
Hey!
みんな、うなたんのオリ曲メドレーどうだった？
Everyone, how did you like Luna-tan's original song medley?
かわいかった？
Was it cute?
ふむふむ、ふむふむ。可愛い可愛い。わかってたのら。
Hmm-hmm, hmm-hmm. Cute, cute. I knew it.
そして、今日のステージを見てください！
And then, please look at today's stage!
デデデデデーン！
Ta-da!
すげー！雲だらけ！
Wow! It's full of clouds!
あっちのほう。
Over there.
この雲の向こう、何があるのなのかな？
I wonder what's beyond these clouds?
みんな予想してみて！
Everyone, try to guess!
そして、今日のライブテーマは、
And then, today's live theme is,
ルーナ・リバース・デイです！
Luna RebirthDay!
どんな意味があるのか。はてさて。
I wonder what kind of meaning it has. Well, let's see.
そして、待ってルーナイト。
And then, wait, LuKnight.
歌ってる時に、うなたん、大変身しました。
While I was singing, Luna-tan went through a big transformation.
みんな気づいてくれたのら？
Did everyone notice?
100万人記念で
For my 1 million subscriber anniversary...
新モデルになりましたー！
...I got a new model!
なんとルーナイトが、うなたんに魔法をかけてくれたのらよね。
The LuKnights cast a spell on Luna-tan, didn't they?
ポリュナイト、ありが。
Polu-Knight, thank...
ポリュ！
Polu!
姫ー！姫ー！ポリュー！姫ー！ポリュー！どこにいんのー？
Hime-! Hime-! Polu-! Hime-! Polu-! Where are you?
わー、この雲の向こうにいます！
Whoa, I'm beyond these clouds!
ポリュ！そうなのらね！
Polu! Is that so?
ねぇねぇ、新しい姿、どう？どう？どう？
Hey, hey, how's my new form? How is it?
えー、めっちゃ可愛いよ！
Whoa, it's super cute!
え、ほんと？
Oh, really?
あのさ、せっかくだから、
You know, since we're here,
姫の以前の姿を出して比較してみよう。
let's bring out Hime's previous form and compare them.
あ、いいね、いいね、いいね！
Oh, that's good, that's good!
ほー！ドコドコドコ、あ、光って出た！
Ho! (Drumroll), oh, it's shining and appearing!
出たパネルが出そう、
A panel is about to appear...
出た出た出た！
...it's out, it's out, it's out!
え、見てどう？
Hey, look, what do you think?
それではまずは足元から見ていきましょう！はい！
Well then, let's start by looking from the feet! Yes!
あ、そうそうそう。あ、比べるといい感じですよ、これ。
Ah, yes, yes. Ah, it looks good when compared, this.
どうだ、どうだ？
How is it?
あー、なんかこれ、影の感じとか変わった？
Ah, did the shadow feel or something change here?
変わった、変わった！あー！スカートとかパニエの感じ変わったね！
It changed, it changed! Ah! The feel of the skirt and panniers changed!
えへへ！
Ehehe!
可愛いねー！いい感じ、いい感じ！
It's cute! Good, good!
あ、待って！ここら辺、ここら辺とか待って、
Ah, wait! Around here, wait around here...
これ、加圧トレーニングの効果出てるんじゃない？
...isn't the effect of the pressure training showing?
出てる、うなたん、出て？最近加圧トレーニングしてる？
It's showing! Have you been doing pressure training lately?
やってるよ！パーソナルだけどな。
I am! Though it's personal training.
あ、そうそう。後ろ向いて、後ろ後ろ。
Ah, right, right. Turn around, turn around.
え、後ろ？およ！
Eh, the back? Oh!
おー！これこれ、ねぇ見てこれ、髪の毛の揺れ！
Oh! This, this, hey look at this, the way the hair sways!
あとシルエットか、これめっちゃいいじゃん！サラサラ！
And the silhouette, this is really good! Smooth!
えへへ、えへへ。
Ehehe, ehehe.
あと、そしてうなたんの手も見てほしいのら。
Also, I want you to look at Luna-tan's hands too.
わー！おててがまあ小さくて可愛いねー！
Whoa! Her hands are so small and cute!
でしょう、手相もいい感じ！
Right? The palm lines look good too!
手相、あ、手相ね。
Palm lines, ah, palm lines.
あと顔見て。
Also, look at the face.
あー！は！お顔、このパネルと比べるとちょっと難しいんだけど。
Ah-! Ha! It's a bit hard to compare the face with this panel, but...
斜めから見た時の、あ、フェイスラインとか変わったね。
When viewed from an angle, ah, the face line and stuff changed.
すげー可愛いじゃん！
It's super cute!
えへへ！パパありがと！
Ehehe! Thanks, Papa!
うん、ぜひみんなもね、
Yeah, I'd definitely like everyone...
過去の3D配信と見比べてほしいのらね。
...to compare it with past 3D streams.
ねぇねぇ、ポリュ、ポリュナイト！おー！
Hey, hey, Polu, Polu-Knight! Oh!
質問があるのだけど、
I have a question...
そっちの雲の向こうってどうなってるのら？
...what's it like beyond those clouds over there?
舞踏会の会場あるよ。来る？
There's a ballroom venue. Want to come?
え、マジ？
Eh, seriously?
いでよ、馬車！
Come forth, carriage!
え、ば、馬車ー？わー、めっちゃ光ってる！
Eh, c-carriage? Whoa, it's glowing so much!
わわわわわ！わわわわわ！
Wawawawawa! Wawawawawa!
でけー！
It's huge!
これムーンギャラクシーの時、ステージにくっついてた馬車なのらよ！
This is the carriage that was attached to the stage during Moon Galaxy!
というわけで姫。乗っちゃってください！
And so, Hime. Please get in!
乗るのら。
I'll get in.
乗ってください！
Please get in!
乗るのらな。
I'm getting in.
うわー、すごーい！中も豪華なのら。
Wow, amazing! The inside is luxurious too.
ちょっとここ座ってみるのら。
I'll try sitting here for a bit.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
ルーナードの人形もあるのらね。
There's even a LuKnight doll.
すごーい！
Amazing!
姫、準備はOKですか？
Hime, are you ready?
もちろん。出発進行なのらなー！
Of course. Full speed ahead!
よし、飛びますよ！
All right, we're taking off!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
うわ！
Whoa!
動いたー！わー、進むぞー！
It moved! Whoa, we're moving!
すげー！この馬車、飛んでるのら！
Amazing! This carriage is flying!
よし。よいしょ、よいしょ。こっち見てみよう。
All right. Heave-ho, heave-ho. Let's look this way.
うわー！すごーい！
Wow! Amazing!
星と雲がめちゃくちゃ綺麗な、のらよ。
The stars and clouds are so incredibly beautiful.
うわー、眺め最高なのらね。
Wow, the view is the best.
ガタンゴトン動いてます。
It's moving with a clatter.
いいのら。
It's nice.
こっちからも見てみるのらね。
Let's look from this side too.
よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
こっちもすごーい！眺め最高！
This side is amazing too! The best view!
おー、いい感じなのらな。
Oh, it feels good.
高いなー、でもここ。
It's high up here, though.
てかポリュナイトさん、このまま進んだら、
By the way, Polu-Knight-san, if we keep going like this...
目の前のデッケー雲とぶつかるのらけどさ。
...we're going to crash into that huge cloud in front of us.
大丈夫なのら？
Is it going to be okay?
進んで、向こうが何も見えないのらよ
Go on, I can't see anything over there-nanora.
いや、ご安心ください。このポルナイトにお任せあれ。
No, please rest assured. Leave it to this Pol-knight.
姫、少々揺れますぞ。
Princess, it's going to shake a little.
しっかり捕まってて下され。
Please hold on tight.
あ、大丈夫？
Ah, are you okay?
本当に大丈夫？
Are you really okay?
行きまーす！
Here we go!
本当に大丈夫？
Are you really okay?
やばいんじゃあないの？
Isn't this bad?
雲、来てるよ。
The clouds are coming.
わっ、わっ、もう、こわいー。
Whoa, whoa, it's scary.
うわぁぁぁー！
Waaaaaah!
あたし今 最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest right now!
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いの
After being dumped by you, I'm at my cutest!
可愛いの
I'm cute,
これが乙女の逆襲だ！
this is a maiden's counterattack!
もう気づいてるかも しれないけど言うわ
You might have noticed already, but I'll say it.
あたしね 今とても
You know, right now I'm very...
かわいい
...cute.
君が始めた恋 君が終わらすなんて
The love you started, you're the one ending it?
何だそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
What's that? I'm gonna cry.
かわいい
Cute.
あたしの連絡だけ通知OFFにしてたなんて
Turning off notifications just for my messages...
友達から聞いたよ
I heard it from a friend.
連絡しすぎだって 君が不安にさせるからじゃん
You said I message too much, but it's because you made me anxious!
もう気にしてないけど だって今
I don't care anymore though, because right now...
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いくなりました
After being dumped by you, I've become the cutest ever!
自分史上1番ときめき放つわ
I'm radiating more excitement than ever before in my life!
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest ever!
認めなよ これが乙女の逆襲だ！
Admit it, this is a maiden's counterattack!
さすがに失恋直後は
As expected, right after the breakup,
涙でぐちゃぐちゃで
I was a mess with tears.
かわいい
Cute.
君が泣かせたのに 雑なサヨナラだった
Even though you made me cry, it was a sloppy goodbye.
何だそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
What's that? I'm gonna cry.
かわいい
Cute.
二人しか知らないって言ってた話だって
Even that story you said only the two of us knew...
どうしてあの子も知ってるの
Why does that girl know it too?
別れてよかったなんて思わせないで欲しかった
I didn't want you to make me feel like it was a good thing we broke up.
好きだったから
Because I loved you.
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いくなりました
After being dumped by you, I've become the cutest ever!
むしろありがと
Actually, thank you.
最上級に可愛いくなったってねえ言って
Hey, tell me I've become the cutest ever!
知って
Know it!
あいつがなんか可愛くなったってねえ聞いて
Hey listen, people are saying she's become pretty cute.
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いの
After being dumped by you, I'm at my cutest!
自分史上1番ときめき放つわ
I'm radiating more excitement than ever before in my life!
最上級に可愛いの
I'm the cutest ever!
認めなよ これが乙女の逆襲だ！
Admit it, this is a maiden's counterattack!
最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest right now!
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いの
After being dumped by you, I'm at my cutest!
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
退屈な月曜日
On a boring Monday,
あなたの香りで目覚めるの
I wake up to your scent.
纏ったトップノート
The top note I wore,
そうよ秘密の物語なの
yes, it's a secret story.
うまくリプライできない
I can't reply well.
震えるハート
Trembling heart,
溜息 恥じらい 空回り
sighing, shyness, spinning my wheels.
誘うファンタジー
Inviting fantasy,
重なっちゃうくらい
so much that we might overlap.
一途だもん
I'm so devoted.
あなたに夢中です♡
I'm crazy about you! ♡
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやんだ！
Ah, I don't want to go viral!
ねえ かまってかまってもっと！
Hey, pay attention to me more!
誰かがあなたを狙っちゃう
Someone's going to aim for you.
ウインク一つでメロメロにさせちゃって
Make them fall head over heels with a single wink,
こっちの気も知らないで
without even knowing how I feel.
もー！バズっちゃバズっちゃやんだ！
Geez! I don't want to go viral!
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと！
Hey, shoot through me forever!
いつでもあなたに惚れ中
I'm always falling for you.
...いたいなー
...I want to be
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a single-minded Cinderella!
どんな道が待ってても
No matter what path lies ahead
ガラスのヒールで駆けてくよ
I'll run in glass heels
魔法が解けても冷めない夢を
A dream that won't end even when the magic fades
あなたにあげるのら
I'll give it to you
だから絶対 負けない！
So I definitely won't lose!
百合結びして 純愛したい
I want to tie a lily knot and have a pure love
まっすぐに
Straight ahead
想うエンパシー 伝わっちゃうくらい
To the point that my empathy is conveyed
本気だもん
Because I'm serious
まさしく無敵ですっ
Truly, I am invincible!
Ah ハマってハマっていいよ ねえ ディグってディグってギュッと
Ah, it's okay to get hooked; hey, dig and dig, then squeeze tight
恋する乙女は変幻自在
A maiden in love is ever-changing
「キレイ」も「ビューティー」も よくばりに励めば
If I greedily strive for both "pretty" and "beauty"
輝く自分になるの
I will become my shining self
さあ！ ハマってハマっていいよ ねえ 気づいて気づいてちゃんと
Come on! It's okay to get hooked; hey, notice me properly
まだまだ乙女は日進月歩
A maiden's progress is still steady
世界で一番のドキドキがほしいの
I want the world's greatest heartbeat
あなただけへのプリンセスです
I am the princess only for you
I love you!
I need you!
Ah 「好き」って「好き」ってなんで そう「好き」って「好き」って言うの
Ah, why do I say "I love you," why do I say "I love you" like that
けなげなココロは困惑中
My devoted heart is in confusion
愛しさふくらんで こんなにも苦しいの
My love is swelling and it's so painful
今すぐこっちに微笑んで
Smile this way right now
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ ねえ かまってかまってもっと
Ah, I don't want to go viral; hey, pay attention to me more
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone will be aiming for you
ウインクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Making everyone fall head over heels with a single wink
あたしの気も知らないで！
Without even knowing how I feel!
もー！ バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ ねえ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと
Geez! I don't want to go viral; hey, pierce through me forever
いつでもあなたに翻弄中
I'm always being toyed with by you
誰よりあなたのトクベツでいたいの
I want to be your special one more than anyone
本音でたかな？ 許してね
Did my true feelings come out? Forgive me
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a single-minded Cinderella!
オトメロディー
Otomelody
スキスキスー フワフワフー こんなキモチ メロメロディ
Suki Suki Su, Fuwa Fuwa Fu, feelings like this, Melo-Melody
夢だけど 夢じゃない お願いね マイメロディ
It's a dream, but not a dream, please, My Melody
オトナじゃない 乙メです
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden
恋するのが仕事です
Falling in love is my job
君の名前つぶやくと ドキドキするの
When I whisper your name, my heart beats fast
聞きわけない この胸が 歌い出して止まらない
This stubborn heart starts singing and won't stop
上手じゃなくてゴメンナサイ
I'm sorry I'm not very good
だけど聞いて とどけ
But listen, let it reach you
マイメロディ マイメロディ マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody, My Melody, My Melody
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
A ribbon crossing the starry sky to protect your dreams
マイメロディ
My Melody
ハート見つけたなら
If I find your heart
グルグル巻きしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it up tight
Wow wow wow 覚悟しといて
Wow wow wow, be prepared
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie
オトナじゃない 乙メです
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I even cry sometimes
女の子って魔法で 作られたの
Girls are made of magic
スキスキスー フワフワフー こんなキモチ メロメロディ
Suki Suki Su, Fuwa Fuwa Fu, feelings like this, Melo-Melody
夢だけど 夢じゃない お願いね マイメロディ
It's a dream, but not a dream, please, My Melody
乙女心
A girl's heart
来る来る恋 つかまえちゃえ
Love is coming, I'll catch it
wow wow wo 逃がさないから
wow wow wo, 'cause I won't let it go
ここへ来て
Come here
キライじゃない ツライです
It's not that I hate it, it's just painful
真っ赤にだってなっちゃいます
I'll even turn bright red
女の子って不思議で作られたの
Girls are made of mysteries
とどけ マイメロディー マイメロディー
Reach out, my melody, my melody
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
Across the starry sky, the ribbon that protects your dreams
マイメロディー ハート見つけたなら
My Melody, if I find a heart
グルグル巻きしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it all around
wow wow wo 覚悟しといて
wow wow wo, be prepared
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a girl
泣いたりだっしちゃいます
I might even cry
女の子って魔法で作られたの
Girls are made of magic
スキスキスー フワフワフー こんなキモチ メロメロディ
Love love love, fluffy fluffy, this feeling, Melo-Melody
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream
お願いね マイメロディー
Please, my melody
マイメロディー
My Melody
わあ！ということで
Wow! And so...
最上級にかわいいのと一途なシンデレラ
"Saijoukyuu ni Kawaii no!" and "Ichizu na Cinderella"...
あとオトメロディー、3曲連続で歌いましたー！
plus "Otomelody", I sang three songs in a row!
ひゃあー！雲が晴れたステージってこうなってるのらねー
Hyaa! So this is what the stage looks like with the clouds cleared!
すっげー！でっけー！武道館みたいなのらねー！
Amazing! It's huge! It's like the Budokan!
あ、ここ見て！シャンデリアがあるのらー！
Oh, look at this! There's a chandelier!
ザ・舞踏会ダンスする場所なのらねー！
It's like a real ballroom dance floor!
あとお城の上の方ってこうなってたんだー！
And so that's what the top of the castle looks like!
見てー！すごいかわいいー！
Look! It's so cute!
しかもこれ、天窓じゃーん！おっしゃれなのらねー！
And look, there's a skylight! How stylish!
すごい！あ、待て、Luna RebirthDayの看板もあるのらー！
Amazing! Oh wait, there's a Luna RebirthDay sign too!
今日はLuna RebirthDayだからな！
Because today is Luna RebirthDay!
見て見て！すごいかわいいー！
Look, look! It's so cute!
最高だったよ、姫！
That was the best, Princess!
え？ルーナイト！何なのらー！
Eh? Lu-Knight! What is it?
実はね、姫にはまだ隠された姿が残されているのです！
Actually, Princess, you still have a hidden form remaining!
ええ？何なのらー！
Eh? What is it?
ルーナイトの魔法でそのお姿にしてみせましょう！
With the Lu-Knight's magic, let us reveal that form!
え？なになになにー！
Eh? What is it, what is it?
デデーン！わあー！すごいかわいい！
Ta-da! Wow! It's so cute!
新しいヘアスタイルなのらなー！
It's a new hairstyle!
ルーナイトがプレゼントしてくれたのらねー！
The Lu-Knights gave it to me as a present!
よし、じゃあこの新しい髪型で歌っちゃうのらー！
All right, then I'll sing with this new hairstyle!
あなたのアイドル さいごはB
Your idol, the last is B
サインはB
The sign is B
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね 待ち遠しくて足をバッタバッタしながら
We finally met, I'm so happy, I was waiting so long, kicking my feet in excitement
今日を楽しみに寝れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep because I was looking forward to today
オレもー！
Me too!
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない 1分1秒無駄になんてできない
There's no time to be nervous, I can't waste a single minute or second
さあ始めましょう
Now, let's begin
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ 「大好き」が集まる場所へようこそ
Clap your hands, welcome, welcome to the place where "love" gathers
日常はクロークの中 ここに来たなら踊らにゃ損 損
Daily life is in the cloakroom, if you're here, you've gotta dance
客席が居ようが居まいが関係ない 会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
It doesn't matter if the seats are full or empty, I don't care if the venue is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる 君のサイリウム
I can see it clearly, your glowstick
今はフーっと吹けば飛ぶような 小さな小さな才能だけど
Right now, it's a tiny, tiny talent that might blow away if you puff at it
私を推してくれるのなら
But if you support me...
If you're going to support me
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you a huge response
アナタのアイドル
Your idol
サインはB
The sign is B
(B小町！ フッフー！)
(B-Komachi! Fu-fu-!)
あいつは俺が育てたって近い将来自慢してほしいよ
I want you to brag in the near future that you're the one who raised her
こうしちゃいられない君と君と今を楽しまなきゃ
We can't just sit here, I have to enjoy the "now" with you and you
引きこもりも人見知りも普段と違う顔見せてよ
Shut-ins and shy people, show me a face different from your usual one
みんな兄弟　調子どうだい　なりふり構わずに
We're all siblings, how's it going? Without caring about appearances
他人に笑われていても関係ない周りがどうとかこうとか気にしない
Even if others laugh at you, it doesn't matter. Don't worry about what those around you say
主張強すぎ　君のサイリウム！
Your light stick stands out too much!
たとえ世界が私を拒んで独りぼっちを感じたとしても
Even if the world rejects me and I feel all alone
アナタが味方でいてくれたら怖いものはないよ
As long as you're on my side, I have nothing to fear
(B小町！ フッフー！)
(B-Komachi! Fu-fu-!)
見てよ見てよ何か始まる君との物語が
Look, look, something is starting. Our story together
嗚呼なんて素晴らしい景色だ！
Ah, what a wonderful sight!
客席が居ようが居まいが関係ない会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
Whether there's an audience or not doesn't matter. I don't care if the venue is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる君のサイリウム！
I can clearly see your light stick!
今はフッと吹けば飛ぶような小さな小さな才能だけど
Right now, it's a tiny, tiny talent that might blow away if you just breathe on it
私を推してくれるのなら
But if you're going to support me
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
If you're on my side
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you a huge response
アナタのアイドル
Your idol
サインはB
The sign is B
(フッフッフー！！)
(Fu-fu-fu-!!)
ロマンスの不祥事　逃がさない
I won't let a romance scandal escape
消してあげる
I'll erase it for you
シル・ヴ・プレジデント
Sil-Vou-President
宣誓！私が大統領になったら人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
Oath! When I become president, any woman who messes with someone else's man will be exiled to an island
宣誓！私が大統領になったら「いやただの友達だよ〜」って誤魔化す奴はヘソから電気を流します
Oath! When I become president, anyone who tries to trick me with "No, we're just friends~" will have electricity run through their belly button
だだだ大胆不敵　センセーショナルクローズアップ
D-D-Daringly fearless, a sensational close-up
D D D Don't cry やるぜ徹底的にリサーチだ
D D D Don't cry, I'm going to do thorough research
大嫌い？　しょうがない？　クズは病気ね　バイバイバイ
Hate it? Can't be helped? Scum is a disease, bye bye bye
権力　財産　地位名声　何にもないけど裁きたいでしょ？
Power, property, status, fame. You have nothing, but you want to judge, right?
だだだ大統領になったらね　まずは君を捕まえるわ
When I become president, first I'll capture you
濡れたタオルで　洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spill everything with a wet towel
誰ですか？あの女
Who is that woman?
ダメですか？そうですか
Not okay? Is that so?
ロマンスの不祥事　逃がさない　消してあげる
I won't let a romance scandal escape, I'll erase it for you
しる・ヴ・ぷれぷれ　プレジデント
Sil-vou-ple-ple President
宣誓！私が大統領になったらただの仕事の付き合いだよって言う奴は二度と働けなくしてやります
Oath! When I become president, anyone who says "It's just for work" will be made unable to work ever again
宣誓！以下略！いや向こうが強引でさ〜っていう男の口にはレジンを流し込んで固めてやります！
Oath! The rest is omitted! Any man who says "No, she was just pushy~", I'll pour resin into his mouth and harden it!
まるでドン・ファン気取りスキャンダラス
Acting like a Don Juan, scandalous
まままま末端価格　甲斐性なしのスクープね
M-M-M-M-Market price, it's a scoop on a worthless person
愛はない？　理由じゃない？　悪くないのに　はいはいはい
No love? Not a reason? Even though it's not bad, yeah yeah yeah
軽薄　脳能　ピチャピチャ　何にもないとかありえないでしょ？
Frivolous, brainless, chatter chatter. There's no way there's nothing, right?
だだだ大統領になってもね　たぶん君は変わらないね
Even if I become president, you probably won't change
しらっととぼけて　のらりくらりかわすのね
Feigning ignorance and dodging me non-committally
デートですか？こんばんは
Is it a date? Good evening
本気ですか？そうですか
Are you serious? Is that so?
情熱とは不注意　微熱も　消してしまいたい
Passion is carelessness, I want to erase even the slight fever
1, 2, 3!
だ だ だ 大統領になったらね
If I became the P-P-P-President,
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'd seriously capture you.
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel,
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spill everything.
(ど・ど・ど！)
(Do, do, do!)
どこですか今あんた
Where are you right now?
見っけちゃった バレちゃった
I found you! You're caught!
夜道にはご用心 さよなら
Watch out on the night roads. Goodbye.
代わりに銃声
Instead, a gunshot—
しる・ヴ・ぷれぷれ プレジデント
S-il vous plait-plait President!
ステップでポップに跳ねさせてチュー
Make it pop with a step and a kiss.
あなた今も忘れたいこと
Are there things you want to forget,
悲しいこと
or sad things,
あるのかしらね
still on your mind?
知らない映画なのに 涙を流すのは
Crying over a movie I don't even know—
ドラマチックが足りてないからよ
it's because there's not enough drama.
そんな風にもつかないこと
Things that just don't fit,
くだらないこと
pointless things,
考えてばかりね
are all you think about.
雨が上がれば愛も空行く顔も
When the rain stops, love and faces in the sky
誰かのもとに なるのでしょう
will likely belong to someone else.
突発のパンデーションも全部 恋のためよ
Sudden foundations are all for the sake of love.
何だかんだどうしてどうして なぜなぜハテナ
No matter what, why oh why, query after query.
不安定なカテーナ どこまで行くの
An unstable catena, where are you going?
あなた一切合切放り去っても
Even if you throw every last thing away,
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
it's no joke, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって どうにもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing you can do.
曖昧な本当なんて メランコリーかするだけ
Vague truths only brush against melancholy.
あたしをさっさ さらって今夜も イエス
Carry me away quickly tonight too, yes.
ああ 全然おかしなハートばかりよ 吐息がびくともしないわ
Ah, it's nothing but strange hearts, my sighs don't even budge.
実体のない感情 放っておいたって 作略なんてありゃせんのになぜ
Even if I ignore my formless emotions, there's no strategy, so why?
ああ もう懲り懲りよ 私の勝手な気質も じっと凝らせ
Ah, I've had enough, let my own selfish disposition freeze still.
取り繕ったってとうとう 臨界点
Even if I gloss it over, it's finally at the critical point.
年がら年中リップサービス 同感かましては平気
Lip service all year round, acting like I agree.
どこ吹く風 昼夜昼下がり 昼から涙の目に物見
A wind from nowhere, afternoon, seeing tears in my eyes since noon.
今やたまさかのミュージックのせいで あなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
Now because of some occasional music, I can't hear a word you're saying.
少しは全うなこと言って イェー
Say something sensible for once, yeah!
回り出したテーブルで 全部忘れさせてよ
Let the spinning table make me forget everything.
だけど一体全体どうしてどうして なぜなぜハテナ
But why on earth, why oh why, query after query.
不安定なカテーナ 消えないままね
The unstable catena remains.
あなた一行(いっこう) 容赦なく突き放しても
Even if you ruthlessly push me away,
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
it's no joke, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって どうにもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing you can do.
曖昧な本当なんて メランコリーかするだけ
Vague truths only brush against melancholy.
あたしを今...
Carry me away now...
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
It's no joke, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって どうにもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing you can do.
不甲斐ないわ 感情なんて何だりかんだり どうしようもないぜ
It's pathetic, emotions and whatnot, there's nothing to be done.
あたしたち 噛み合っている マジ
We're perfectly in sync, seriously.
アイアイヤ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Ai-ai-ya, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって どうにもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing you can do.
曖昧な本当なんて メランコリーかするだけ
Vague truths only brush against melancholy.
あたしをさっさ さらって今夜も イエス
Carry me away quickly tonight too, yes.
二酸化炭素を吐き出して
Exhaling carbon dioxide,
あの子が呼吸をしているよ
that child is breathing.
曇天模様の空の下
Under the cloudy sky,
つぼみのままで揺れながら
swaying as a bud.
野良犬は僕の骨くわえ
A stray dog chews on my bone,
野性の力をためしてる
testing its wild power.
路地裏に月がおっこちて
The moon falls in the back alley,
犬の目玉は四角だよ
and the dog's eyeballs are square.
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, humanity for the first time
木星についたよ
reached Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
is drawing near.
さよなら人類
Goodbye Humanity
アラビヤの 笛の音響く
The sound of an Arabian flute echoes
街のはずれの 夢のあと
A trace of a dream on the outskirts of town
翼をなくした ペガサスが
A Pegasus who has lost its wings
夜空に はしごかけている
Is placing a ladder against the night sky
武器をかついだ 兵隊さん
A soldier carrying weapons
南に行こうと してるけど
Is trying to go south, but
サーベルの音は チャラチャラと
The sound of his saber goes clink-clink
街の空気を 汚してる
And is polluting the town's air
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星に ついたよ
Reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスに なる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near
歌を忘れたカナリヤ
The canary that forgot its song
牛を忘れた牛小屋
The cowshed that forgot its cows
壊れた磁石を 拾い集める
Gathering broken magnets
博士は まるはげさ
The professor is completely bald
あの子は 花火を打ち上げて
That girl set off fireworks
この日が来たのを 祝ってる
Celebrating the arrival of this day
冬の花火は 強すぎて
The winter fireworks are too strong
ぼくらの体は くだけ散る
Our bodies shatter and scatter
ブーゲンビリアの 木の下で
Under the bougainvillea tree
ぼくはあの子を 探すけど
I look for that girl, but
月の光に 邪魔されて
Obstructed by the moonlight
あの子のかけらは 見つからない
Her fragments cannot be found
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星に ついたよ
Reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスに なる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星に ついたよ
Reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスに なる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near
さるには なりたくない
I don't want to become a monkey
壊れた磁石を 砂浜で
Searching for broken magnets on the beach
拾っているだけさ
I'm just picking them up
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星に ついたよ
Reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスに なる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near
さるに なるよ
I'll become a monkey
サンドリヨン
作詞：orange　作曲：Dios/シグナルP
Cendrillon
Lyrics: orange  Composition: Dios/Signal-P
朝まで踊る 夢だけ見せて
Let me dream only of dancing until morning
時計の鐘が 魔法を
The clock's chime [breaks] the magic
曖昧な指 誘う階段
Vague fingers, enticing stairs
三段飛ばしに 跳ねていく
Leaping up three steps at a time
馬車の中で 震えてた
I was trembling inside the carriage
みじめな古着 めくりめくれよ
Turn over, turn over those miserable old clothes
舞踏会
The ball
見知らぬ顔探す
Searching for an unfamiliar face
囁くあの声が
That whispering voice
握り締めた刃
The blade held tight
突き立てて
Thrust into place
すべてを奪えと
Telling me to take everything
孤児（こじ）　集う城
The castle where orphans gather
笑み仮面に描いて
Painting a smile on a mask
偽りの慈しみさえ
Even false affection
羽で包む
Is enveloped with wings
熾天使（セラフ）
Seraph
灰の中で
Within the ashes
赤く溶けて
Melting red
混じる
Mixing in
硝子の靴
The glass slipper
今さら帰る
Returning now
震えているの
I am trembling
あなたが目をやる時計
The clock you glance at
靴脱ぎ踊る
Dancing without shoes
スロープ抜けて
Through the slope
喉まで伸びる
Extending to the throat
指の先で
At the tips of fingers
すくう滴
Scooping up droplets
口付けて
Kissing them
走る衝動
A running impulse
背骨抜けていく
Goes through the spine
刹那
In an instant
鐘は
Don't let
鳴らさないで
the bell ring
あなたにひざまずき
Kneeling before you
まだダメと叫んだ
The right hand that cried
右手が
"Not yet"
突き刺すサヨナラ
Stabs a goodbye
消せない硝煙を
Wearing indelible gunpowder smoke
香水にまとう姫
as perfume, the princess
強い瞳　僕の凍った
Strong eyes shoot through
仮面ごと
even my frozen mask
撃ち抜く
And all
今も
Even
耳に
now
あなたの
your breath
吐息が
is in my ears
突き刺さるの
Stabbing into
遠い
a distant
夢
dream
ステンドグラスごし
Through the stained glass
光る月が
the shining moon
君にかぶせた
placed a veil
ベール
over you
ドレス
Tearing
膝で裂いて
the dress at the knee
ティアラは
The tiara
投げ捨てて
is thrown away
見つめあう
The eyes
瞳と瞳が
looking at each other
火花を放つ
Emit sparks
孤独な
Lonely
魂が
souls
炎あげ
catch fire
惹かれあう
and are drawn to each other
その涙
If those tears
すくえないなら
cannot be scooped up
まるで
It is just like
一人遊び
playing alone
時よ止まれ今は
Time, stop now
あなたに酔いしれて
Drunk on you
揺れる鼓動
Every single
一つ一つを
shaking heartbeat
刻み付けてたい
I want to engrave
とどまれ
Stay
熱く濡れ
hot and wet
打ち付ける高まりに
In the striking surge
これ以上は
I can't move
動けないよ
any more
まるで
Like a
御伽噺（フェアリーテイル）
Fairy Tale
みんな、ここからは大事な告知タイムなのな！
Everyone, it's time for some important announcements!
ポルポル、そこで見ててなのなね！
Pol-Pol, watch from over there, okay!
では、まずはこちら！
Now, first up is this!
姫森ルーナ誕生日記念2025のグッズだっまーす！
Himekiri Luna Birthday Celebration 2025 goods are here!
ではね、こちら詳細見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a look at the details!
ふたりのルーナ、アクリルジオラマスタンドなのな！
The "Two Lunas" Acrylic Diorama Stand!
イラストは、ソイルン先生に書いていただきました。
The illustration was drawn by Soilu-sensei.
前のね、髪型と今回のルーナの新しい髪型のルーナが...
It features Luna with her previous hairstyle and this new one...
そして、今回の生誕ライブのステージに登場しました。
And the stage from today's birthday live is included.
こちらはね、立体的なパーツが華やかで可愛い素敵な豪華仕様のジオラマスタンドになっております。
This is a wonderful, luxuriously specified diorama stand with gorgeous and cute 3D parts.
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ、守ってル一ナイトver.！
Himekiri Luna Plushie, "Protect the Lu-Knight" ver.!
姫森ルーナの生誕記念グッズが届きました！
Himemori Luna's birthday celebration goods have arrived!
「守ってルーナイト」の衣装のんなたんが、ぬいぐるみになりました！
Luna-tan in her "Protect the Luna-knight" outfit has become a plushie!
ぜひぜひ、みんなおうちにお迎えして、んなたんを守ってほしいのならよ。
Please, everyone, welcome her into your home and protect Luna-tan!
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
デデン！ルーナイト2wayバッグ！
Ta-da! Luna-knight 2-way bag!
さっきのぬいぐるみもすっぽり入ってしまう、ルーナイトがアピールできるバッグになたります。
The plushie from before fits perfectly inside; it's a bag that lets you show off being a Luna-knight.
バッグはね、なんとリュックにもなって超便利！
The bag can also be used as a backpack, making it super convenient!
デザインに使用されているモチーフは、ルーナイト由来のもので統一しているので、バッグモードでもリュックモードでもお好きな方で使ってくなさい。
The motifs used in the design are all derived from Luna-knights, so please use it in either bag or backpack mode as you like!
デデン！ルーナイトカードホルダー！
Ta-da! Luna-knight card holder!
ルーナイト型のカードホルダーです。
It's a Luna-knight shaped card holder.
チェキ風カードやホロカのカードも入れられちゃうので、ルーナイトのみんなはこっちもしっかり守ってくなさいね。
You can even put Cheki-style cards or Holo-cards in it, so Luna-knights, please protect these well too.
そして、次はこちら！デデン！
And next is this! Ta-da!
ASMRボイス「舞踏会の帰り道」
ASMR Voice: "The Way Home from the Ball"
今回はね、舞踏会をイメージした生誕祭ライブなので、ルーナイトと帰路についたひとときをボイスにしました。
Since this birthday live is themed after a ball, I made a voice recording of a moment spent heading home with a Luna-knight.
馬車の中という密室で、なんか急接近とかあったりしちゃうかも？
Inside the enclosed space of a carriage, maybe there will be some close encounters?
ということで、最後に改めてフルセットを見てみましょう！
So, let's take one last look at the full set!
こちら、フルセット購入特典は...
The bonus for purchasing the full set is...
デデン！オリジナルカード！
Ta-da! Original card!
イラストはジョイレン先生で、表面がチェキ風のカードになってます。裏面は招待状風のデザインになっていてオシャレななら。
The illustration is by Joilen-sensei, and the front is a Cheki-style card. The back has a stylish invitation-like design.
そして、通常バージョンのフルセット購入特典は、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード。
And the standard version full set purchase bonus is a foil-stamped replica signed Cheki-style bromide card.
そして、数量限定バージョンのフルセット購入特典は、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードならら。
And the limited-quantity version full set purchase bonus is a hand-signed Cheki-style bromide card!
みんな、ゲットしてほしいのなら。
I hope everyone gets one.
グッズはね、配信終了後販売開始です。
The goods will go on sale after the stream ends.
そしてそして、もう一つ大事なお知らせがあります。こちら！
And furthermore, there's another important announcement. This!
「んなっしょいぱっしょん」！
"Nnasyoi Passion"!
こちらをね、この後歌わせていただきます。
I'll be singing this song for you later.
みんな大好きな「んなっしょい」という言葉を使っているのでね、みんなこの後いっぱいんなっしょいしなー！
It uses the word "Nnasyoi" that everyone loves, so everyone, let's "Nnasyoi" a lot after this!
この配信が終わったら、MVも公開されます。
Once this stream is over, the MV will also be released.
そして、MV公開後、面源が今回初めてやることになったので、こちらもお楽しみに！
And after the MV release, I'll be doing a member-only stream for the first time, so look forward to that too!
ではね、歌います！「んなっしょいぱっしょん」！
Well then, I'm going to sing! "Nnasyoi Passion"!
んなんなんなっしょい！
Nna-nna-nnasyoi!
べつにおーじとかねーのら！
I don't really have a prince or anything!
むにゃむにゃ目をこする
Rubbing my half-asleep eyes
とらわれた城にパーフェクトな朝
A perfect morning in the captive castle
おーないおーないお布団を
Oh night, oh night, out of the futon...
飛び出して海へ行こう
...I'll jump and head to the sea!
神様だって間違うんだって
They say even God makes mistakes
よくある話だそうです
Apparently, it's a common story
姫様に見とれちゃんだって
They say they're captivated by the princess
やれやれなのらね
Good grief, isn't it?
夢を夢見て
Dreaming a dream
恋に恋して生きていたい
I want to live while being in love with love
だから
So
これでいいのら！
This is just fine!
んなんなんな泣きたい！腹わらいたい！
Nna-nna-nna, I want to cry! My stomach's laughing!
こころだっておりゃって変えるのら！
I'll even change my heart with a "heave-ho"!
だから会いたい その願いに
So I want to see you; in that wish...
いま約束の合言葉
...now, the promised password
いくよっ
Here we go!
んなっしょい！！
Nnasyoi!!
まどろみもホラーな夜もあるけど
There are slumbering nights and horror nights too
でもね
But you see
んなっしょい！！
Nnasyoi!!
いつまでもみんなおりゅから平気
Since everyone's always here, it's okay
まだ遊び足りねーのら！
I haven't played enough yet!
こない こない 夜の中
In the night that won't come, won't come
ティアラをはずして 城を抜けたら
I'll take off my tiara and slip out of the castle
深い 深い 海に出て
Heading out to the deep, deep sea
...バレてんのら！ぐっどないとー
...Did you find out? Good night!
姫様はね わがままなーんて
Princesses are, you know, selfish...
おとぎ話よ そうでしょ？
That's a fairy tale, right?
何がなんだって 私なんだって
No matter what, I am who I am
これでいいのら！
This is just fine!
んなんななりたい 私でいたい
I want to become "Nna-nna", I want to be myself
どこへだって 向かってゆけるのら
I can head anywhere!
ならばさあない この想いに
Then there's no choice for these feelings
今 許される 合言葉
The password that's allowed now
行くよっ！ んなっしょい！！
Here we go! Nanshoi!!
サンゴ礁 白い砂浜も綺麗
Coral reefs, the white sandy beaches are also beautiful
そこに んなっしょい！！
Over there, Nanshoi!!
んなっしょい！！ んなっしょい！！
Nanshoi!! Nanshoi!!
輝く私
The shining me
Q. 帰る理由は？
Q. The reason for going home?
A. そこになければ ねぇのら！
A. If it's not there, there isn't one!
んなぁぁあぃ！
Nnaaaai!
りぴーと あふた みー！
Repeat after me!
んなっしょい！ んなっしょい！
Nanshoi! Nanshoi!
せーの！
Ready, go!
んなっしょい！ んなっしょい！
Nanshoi! Nanshoi!
もう１回！
One more time!
んなっしょい！ んなっしょい！
Nanshoi! Nanshoi!
いいねぇ！
Nice!
熱い視線が集中
Hot gazes are concentrating
ハラハラする心に無我夢中
Absorbed in a heart-pounding heart
だから だから
So, so
これでいいのら！
This is just fine!
んなんな泣きたい から笑いたい
I want to cry "Nna-nna", so I want to laugh
心だって奪ってあげるのら
I'll even steal your heart!
だから会いたい その願いに
So I want to see you, for that wish
今 約束の 合言葉
The password of promise now
行くよっ！ んなっしょい！！
Here we go! Nanshoi!!
まどろみも ホラーな夜もあるけれど
There are slumbers and horror nights, too
でもね んなっしょい！！
But you know, Nanshoi!!
この先もみんな おりゅから平気
Since everyone's here from now on, I'm okay
まだ遊び足りねぇのら
I haven't played enough yet!
生誕ライブ見に来てくれてありがとうなのら...！
Thanks for coming to see my birthday live...!
今年は体調不良の時期もあったから
声が出せなかったかもしれない...てか
Since there were times I was feeling unwell this year,
maybe I wouldn't have been able to use my voice... I mean,
でも最後まで頑張ったのら！！ふんぬー！！
But I did my best until the end!! Funnuu!!
これからもずっとずっと姫様に更なる忠誠を
Continue to show even more loyalty to the Princess forever and ever.
I Love You ちゅぱちゅぱ (•ө•)♡
I Love You *chupa chupa* (•ө•)♡
2025.10.10 るーなより
2025.10.10 From Luna